<!DOCTYPE ROOT PUBLIC "-//Carswell//DTD Precedent Keying//EN">
<ROOT>
<COURTFILE ID="2019CarswellOnt7579">
<PLEADING LABEL="Pleading" TYPE="PLEADING"><N>PT1.1</N>
<GRAPHIC FILENAME="2019CARSWELLONT7579PT1.1.PDF"><LINKTEXT>Original Image of this Document (PDF)</LINKTEXT></GRAPHIC>
<SUBTYPE>Claim or Originating Document</SUBTYPE>
<DOCTI>Statement of Claim</DOCTI>
<SUBJECT>Corporate and Commercial</SUBJECT>
<SUBJECT>Torts</SUBJECT>
<SUBJECT>Employment</SUBJECT>
<DATE YYYYMMDD="20190510" LABEL="Date: ">10-May-2019</DATE>
<CASEREF><SOC>2298679 Ontario Inc. et al. v. Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. et al.</SOC><CITE>2019 CarswellOnt 7579</CITE></CASEREF>
<DOCKET>*****START OF COURT DOCUMENT*****</DOCKET>
<DOCKET LABEL="Court File No.: ">CV-19-00619754-0000</DOCKET>
<COURTJUR>ONTARIO SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE</COURTJUR>
<PARTYBLOCK>
<PARTY>2298679 ONTARIO INC. DBA AURUM PROPERTY CARE (PREVIOUSLY DBA GOLD STANDARD PROPERTY CARE)</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Plaintiff</PARTYROLE>
<CONNECTOR>and</CONNECTOR>
<PARTY>NORTHERN HOMECARE SOLUTIONS INC., JOSHUA GOLDKIND, JOSHUA GOLDMAN, JARED HYDE, ANDREW AROUS and RYAN EDWARDS</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Defendants</PARTYROLE>
</PARTYBLOCK>
<COUNSELBLOCK>
<LAWFIRM>
<FIRMNAME>ROSS BARRISTERS, PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</FIRMNAME>
</LAWFIRM>
<ADDRESS>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON</LINE>
<LINE>M5V 2E2</LINE>
</ADDRESS>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Mark A.</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Ross</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 50872U</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Sarah</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Walker</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 62427H</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE>
<LINE>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</LINE>
</COUNSELBLOCK>
<FREEFORM>
<BLOCK1><TI>STATEMENT OF CLAIM</TI>
<P>TO THE DEFENDANTS</P>
<P>A LEGAL PROCEEDING HAS BEEN COMMENCED AGAINST YOU by the Plaintiff. The Claim made against you is set out in the following pages.</P>
<P>IF YOU WISH TO DEFEND THIS PROCEEDING, you or an Ontario lawyer acting for you must prepare a Statement of Defence in Form 18A prescribed by the Rules of Civil Procedure, serve it on the Plaintiff's lawyer or, where the Plaintiff does not have a lawyer, serve it on the Plaintiff, and file it, with proof of service in this court office, WITHIN TWENTY DAYS after this Statement of Claim is served on you, if you are served in Ontario.</P>
<P>If you are served in another province or territory of Canada or in the United States of America, the period for serving and filing your Statement of Defence is forty days. If you are served outside Canada and the United States of America, the period is sixty days.</P>
<P>Instead of serving and filing a Statement of Defence, you may serve and file a Notice of Intent to Defend in Form 18B prescribed by the Rules of Civil Procedure. This will entitle you to ten more days within which to serve and file your Statement of Defence.</P>
<P>IF YOU FAIL TO DEFEND THIS PROCEEDING, JUDGMENT MAY BE GIVEN AGAINST YOU IN YOUR ABSENCE AND WITHOUT FURTHER NOTICE TO YOU. IF YOU WISH TO DEFEND THIS PROCEEDING BUT ARE UNABLE TO PAY LEGAL FEES, LEGAL AID MAY BE AVAILABLE TO YOU BY CONTACTING A LOCAL LEGAL AID OFFICE.</P>
<P>TAKE NOTICE: THIS ACTION WILL AUTOMATICALLY BE DISMISSED if it has not been set down for trial or terminated by any means within five years after the act ion was commenced unless otherwise ordered by the court.</P>
<P>Date &ellip35;</P>
<P>Issued by &ellip35;</P>
<P>Local Registrar</P>
<P>Address of court office:
<LINE>Superior Court of Justice</LINE>
<LINE>393 University Avenue, 10th Floor</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON M5G 1E6</LINE></P>
<P>TO:
<LINE>Northern Homecare Solutions Inc.</LINE>
<LINE>1001 Finch Avenue West, Suite 200 A</LINE>
<LINE>North York, ON M3J 2C7</LINE></P>
<P>AND TO:
<LINE>Joshua Goldkind</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE></P>
<P>AND TO:
<LINE>Joshua Goldman</LINE>
<LINE>1001 Finch Avenue West, Suite 200A</LINE>
<LINE>North York, ON M3J 2C7</LINE></P>
<P>AND TO:
<LINE>Jared Hyde</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE></P>
<P>AND TO:
<LINE>Andrew Arous</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE></P>
<P>AND TO:
<LINE>Ryan Edwards</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE>
<LINE>[location omitted]</LINE></P></BLOCK1>
<BLOCK1><TI>CLAIM</TI>
<P>1. The Plaintiff, 2298679 Ontario Inc. claims:
<P1>(a) An interim, interlocutory and permanent injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information in any form or through any medium whatsoever;</P1>
<P1>(b) an Order requiring all the Defendants to preserve and return to Aurum any and all materials, information and data, however stored or maintained, containing Aurum information that was improperly obtained;</P1>
<P1>(c) an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> Order permitting the Plaintiff to search for, identify, inspect, preserve, reproduce, and remove into the custody of an independent lawyer, any and all documents, items, devices, equipment, and any component thereof, which are believed to contain evidence relevant to this Action, to be detailed by the Plaintiff;</P1>
<P1>(d) an Order requiring the Defendants to provide a complete accounting of: all Aurum customers who they have contacted; all Aurum customers who they have made a booking with; all Aurum customers who they have serviced this year, nature of the services provided, date and price;</P1>
<P1>(e) actual and punitive damages in an amount to be determined by the Court for Hyde, Arous and Edwards' past and ongoing breaches of confidence and breaches of contract;</P1>
<P1>(f) actual and punitive damages in an amount to be determined by the Court for the torts of conversion and conspiracy in connection with Hyde, Arous and Edwards' transfer of confidential customer and related information to Northern Homecare Solutions Inc., Joshua Goldkind and/or Joshua Goldman;</P1>
<P1>(g) damages for conversion, corporate theft and conspiracy committed by all the Defendants in connection with the use and misuse of confidential customer information of the Plaintiff;</P1>
<P1>(h) actual and punitive damages in an amount to be determined by the Court for impersonating the Plaintiff;</P1>
<P1>(i) an accounting with respect to all monies received by these Defendants or any of them in connection with work or services provided to the customers and former customers of the Plaintiff;</P1>
<P1>(j) punitive or exemplary damages in an amount to be determined by the Court;</P1>
<P1>(k) prejudgment interest in accordance with section 128 of the <EM>Courts of Justice Act</EM>, R.S.O. 1990, c. C.43, as amended;</P1>
<P1>(l) postjudgment interest in accordance with section 129 of the <EM>Courts of Justice Act</EM>, R.S.O. 1990, c. C.43, as amended;</P1>
<P1>(m) the costs of this action on a substantial indemnity basis, plus all applicable taxes.</P1></P>
<BLOCK2><TI>The parties</TI>
<P>2. 2298679 Ontario Inc. is an Ontario company, with its head office in Toronto, Ontario. 2298679 Ontario Inc. carried on business as Gold Standard Property Care until October 30, 2017, when it began carrying on business as Aurum Property Care (&ldquo;<BOLD>Aurum</BOLD>&rdquo;). For simplicity, 2298679 Ontario Inc. is referred to as either the Plaintiff or Aurum throughout this claim.</P>
<P>3. Aurum is a leading Canadian commercial and residential window cleaning and property maintenance company. Aurum is an industry leader servicing government contracts, commercial high-rise buildings, condominium towers, hotels and hospitals, among others.</P>
<P>4. The Defendant Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. (&ldquo;<BOLD>Northern Homecare</BOLD>&rdquo;) is an Ontario company based out of Thornhill, Ontario and incorporated April 19, 2018. Northern Homecare has advertised and operated its business through the websites the websites www.northerninfo.com, www.northernhomeservices.com and www.northern-homecare.com.</P>
<P>5. The website www.northerninfo.com is registered to Joshua Goldkind at the address 1206 Centre Street, Thornhill, Ontario. The website www.northernhomeservices.com lists the executive team as Joshua Goldkind, Joshua Goldman, Gabriel Jablonski and Nicholas Hatsios.</P>
<P>6. The Defendant Joshua Goldkind resides in Thornhill, Ontario. He is the founder and Chief Executive Officer of Northern Homecare.</P>
<P>7. The Defendant Joshua Goldman resides in Thornhill, Ontario. He is Northern Homecare's Chief Operations Officer.</P>
<P>8. The Defendant Jared Hyde is a former employee of the Plaintiff. He worked for the Plaintiff from May 1, 2017 to August 25, 2018. Hyde was a field business development manager. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.</P>
<P>9. The Defendant Andrew Arous is a former employee of the Plaintiff. He worked for the Plaintiff from April 1, 2018 to July 6, 2018. He was a field business development representative. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.</P>
<P>10. The Defendant Ryan Edwards is a former employee of the Plaintiff. He worked for the Plaintiff from April 1, 2018 to August 2, 2018. He started as a field business development representative and then moved into the role of outbound business development representative. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.</P></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI>Hyde, Arous and Edwards' terms of employment</TI>
<P>11. The terms of Hyde, Arous and Edwards' employment and their obligations to Aurum were governed by their respective offers of employment and the implied terms of their employment.</P>
<P>12. The terms of Hyde, Arous and Edwards' employment, as laid out in their respective employment agreements, included clear and express obligations to protect Aurum's proprietary and confidential information during and after their employment with Aurum.</P>
<P>13. At all times, Hyde, Arous and Edwards were aware of the confidential and proprietary nature of the information to which they had access through their employment, and they knew and appreciated the importance that Aurum placed on safeguarding its confidential and proprietary information.</P></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI>Hyde, Arous and Edwards improperly accessed and disseminated Aurum data</TI>
<P>14. Hyde, Arous and Edwards have each improperly accessed, disclosed, transmitted, misappropriated, disseminated and/or misused Aurum's confidential and proprietary information following the end of their respective employment terms.</P>
<P>15. The full extent of the information accessed, disclosed, transmitted, misappropriated, disseminated and misused, and all of the locations where it is stored are not known to Aurum. The particulars of the breaches known to Aurum at this time are as follows.
<P1>(a) Hyde accessed and edited various Google spreadsheets containing confidential Aurum information on his Aurum account after his termination on August 25, 2018. The documents that Hyde accessed are:
<P2>(1) &ldquo;Door-to-Door Inbound Calls&rdquo; accessed on September 17, 2018;</P2>
<P2>(2) &ldquo;Outbound Calls&rdquo; accessed on October 30, 2018;</P2>
<P2>(3) &ldquo;Sales deductions scenarios&rdquo; accessed and edited on November 18, 2018;</P2>
<P2>(4) &ldquo;Outbound Call Sheet&rdquo; accessed on January 29, 2019;</P2>
<P2>(5) &ldquo;Gold Standard Sales&rdquo; edited twice on February 19, 2019 at 10:20 AM and at 1:50 PM; and</P2>
<P2>(6) &ldquo;Jared Outbound&rdquo; edited twice on February 19, 2019 at 10:33 AM and 2:21 PM, and accessed four more times, on March 1, 4, 21 and 22, 2019.</P2></P1>
<P1>(b) After they were terminated, Hyde, Arous and Edwards each improperly accessed Aurum's customer relationship management software (called the Window Cleaning Management System or the &ldquo;<BOLD>WCMS</BOLD>&rdquo;) as follows:
<P2>(i) Hyde logged into the WCMS 40 times. The first time he logged into the WCMS post-termination was September 5, 2018, and the most recent time was April 9, 2019;</P2>
<P2>(ii) Andrew Arous logged into the WCMS on at least six occasions: August 29, 2018, December 13, 2018 and February 5, March 15, 19 and 26, 2019; and</P2>
<P2>(iii) Ryan Edwards logged into the WCMS on at least two occasions, both on March 5, 2019.</P2></P1></P></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI>Northern employees impersonated Aurum</TI>
<P>16. The Defendants Northern Homecare, Goldkind and/or Goldman obtained Aurum customer information from Hyde, Arous and/or Edwards. They contacted Aurum customers falsely representing to these customers that Aurum had changed its business name to Northern Homecare, and that they were the representatives of Aurum, with whom these customers have dealt with in the past.</P>
<P>17. In their communications with Aurum's customers, Northern Homecare, Goldkind and /or Goldman referenced details of past services rendered by Aurum that only an Aurum employee would have access to, including names, telephone numbers, addresses, nature of previous year's service, date of previous year's service and exact price of last service.</P>
<P>18 These Defendants utilized the aforesaid confidential information in order to obtain for themselves and for the benefit of their co-Defendants the benefit, goodwill and contractual relationships with its customers that Aurum developed over a number of years at substantial expense.</P>
<P>19. Full particulars of such misrepresentations are within the knowledge of the Defendants and are not yet in the knowledge of the Plaintiff. Examples of such misrepresentations include:
<P1>(a) on April 9, 2019, Aurum customer David Shum exchanged emails with Josh at Northern Homecare, who introduced himself as having done Mr. Shum's eaves cleaning the year before. Josh said that Northern Homecare was related to Aurum, and that &ldquo;[t]here were problems last year with the operation, so we restructured the operations this year and it is called Northern Home Care now.&rdquo; This was patently false;</P1>
<P1>(b) on March 22, 2019, Aurum customer Natalia Duszka advised Aurum that she received a telephone call from a person named Josh who said he was taking over Aurum's clients from last year. There is no person named Josh currently employed by Aurum to do sales calls; and</P1>
<P1>(c) on April 29, 2019, Aurum customer Danny Couture reported that he had received a call from someone to rebook a cleaning job (which it turned out Aurum had already completed). Mr. Couture reported that the call for rebooking had come from the phone number [#omitted], and that when he called the number back, a person answered and identified their business as Northern Homecare.</P1></P>
<P>20. The full extent and details of the Defendants' wrongful conduct are within the knowledge of the Defendants and are not known to Aurum.</P>
<P>21. By transmitting, possessing, storing and disclosing the confidential Aurum data, the defendants have unlawfully misappropriated proprietary and confidential information belonging to Aurum.</P>
<P>22. The misappropriation of Aurum's data has damaged Aurum's reputation, has resulted in a direct loss of revenue, and has also compromised Aurum's ability to sell its customer list, which Aurum has been actively trying to sell.</P>
<P>23. The threat to Aurum's interests and the damage suffered by it are ongoing.</P></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI>Damages and relief sought</TI>
<P>24. <BOLD><EM>Breach of confidence</EM></BOLD>. By transmitting, storing and disclosing confidential and proprietary information belonging to Aurum, Hyde, Arous and Edwards breached their employment agreements and their implied terms of employment. They knew the information that they transmitted, stored and disclosed was confidential and proprietary in nature. In so doing, they misused confidential information, committing a breach of confidence.</P>
<P>25. <BOLD><EM>Tort of conversion and interference with Aurum's right of exclusive possession</EM></BOLD>. Aurum has the exclusive right to possession of its confidential customer information. By wrongfully possessing, storing, and disclosing confidential and proprietary data belonging to Aurum, the Defendants committed the tort of conversion. The disclosure of this information was wrongful interference with Aurum's right of exclusive possession.</P>
<P>26. <BOLD><EM>Unlawful civil conspiracy</EM></BOLD>. In taking steps to wrongfully transmit, possess, store, and disclose the confidential Aurum data, the Defendants have engaged in concerted action each with the others pursuant to an agreement reached among them which constitutes an unlawful civil conspiracy.</P>
<P>27. The Defendants were and are motivated to conspire for the predominant and common purpose of using the confidential and proprietary Aurum data for their own purposes. The transmission, possession, storage and disclosure of the confidential Aurum data constitute unlawful conduct, all which the Defendants did in furtherance of their unlawful conspiracy.</P>
<P>28. The Defendants' conduct has at all times been directed at Aurum. They knew or ought to have known that as a result of their conspiracy, Aurum would suffer damage and loss. Aurum has in fact suffered damage and loss as a result of the conspiracy by, and unlawful acts of, the Defendants. The particulars of this damage and loss are to be further particularized at trial, and include loss of revenue, harm to Aurum's goodwill, competitive advantage, reputation, and ability to sell its residential customer list.</P>
<P>29. The extent of the damage caused by the Defendants cannot yet be determined. The quantum will be determined before trial.</P>
<P>30. The Plaintiff requires the Defendants to provide a complete accounting of all customers serviced by them this year, nature of work done, date and price, so that the Defendant can establish immediate steps to be taken to rectify the damage done by the Defendants to the Plaintiff's business.</P>
<P>31. Aurum requests that this action be tried at Toronto, Ontario.</P>
<P><EM>(Date of issue)</EM></P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>ROSS BARRISTERS</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON M5V 2E2</LINE></P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>Mark A. Ross LSO# 50872U</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>Sarah Walker LSO# 62427H</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE></P>
<P><LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE></P>
<P>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</P></BLOCK2></BLOCK1>
</FREEFORM>
</PLEADING>
<FACTUM LABEL="Factum" TYPE="INTERLOCUTORY"><N>M1.F1</N>
<GRAPHIC FILENAME="2019CARSWELLONT7579M1.F1.PDF"><LINKTEXT>Original Image of this Document (PDF)</LINKTEXT></GRAPHIC>
<DOCTI>Factum of the Plaintiff</DOCTI>
<SUBJECT>Corporate and Commercial</SUBJECT>
<SUBJECT>Torts</SUBJECT>
<SUBJECT>Employment</SUBJECT>
<STATREF><TI>Rules of Civil Procedure</TI>
<REFN>Rule ^RRO1990r194 37.07(2)</REFN></STATREF>
<DATE YYYYMMDD="20190513" LABEL="Date: ">13 May, 2019</DATE>
<CASEREF><SOC>2298679 Ontario Inc. et al. v. Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. et al.</SOC><CITE>2019 CarswellOnt 7579</CITE></CASEREF>
<DOCKET>*****START OF COURT DOCUMENT*****</DOCKET>
<DOCKET LABEL="Court File No. ">CV-19-00619754-00</DOCKET>
<COURTJUR>ONTARIO SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE</COURTJUR>
<PARTYBLOCK>
<LINE>BETWEEN:</LINE>
<PARTY>2298679 ONTARIO INC. DBA AURUM PROPERTY CARE (FORMERLY DBA GOLD STANDARD PROPERTY CARE)</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Plaintiff</PARTYROLE>
<CONNECTOR>and</CONNECTOR>
<PARTY>NORTHERN HOMECARE SOLUTIONS INC., JOSHUA GOLDKIND, JOSHUA GOLDMAN, JARED HYDE, ANDREW AROUS and RYAN EDWARDS</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Defendants</PARTYROLE>
</PARTYBLOCK>
<COUNSELBLOCK>
<LAWFIRM>
<FIRMNAME>ROSS BARRISTERS, PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</FIRMNAME>
</LAWFIRM>
<ADDRESS>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON</LINE>
<LINE>M5V 2E2</LINE>
</ADDRESS>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Mark A.</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Ross</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 50872U</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Sarah</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Walker</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 62427H</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE>
<LINE>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</LINE>
</COUNSELBLOCK>
<INTERNALTOC><TI>Included Documents</TI>
<TOCP TOCIDREF="I">PART I&mdash;Overview</TOCP>
<TOCP TOCIDREF="II">PART II&mdash;Facts</TOCP>
<TOCP TOCIDREF="III">PART III&mdash;Statement of Issues, Law &amp; Authorities</TOCP>
<TOCP TOCIDREF="IV">PART IV&mdash;Order Requested</TOCP></INTERNALTOC>
<FREEFORM>
<BLOCK1><TI>FACTUM OF THE PLAINTIFF</TI>
<P>May 13, 2019</P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>ROSS BARRISTERS</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON M5V 2E2</LINE></P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>Mark A. Ross LSO# 50872U</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>Sarah Walker LSO# 62427H</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE></P>
<P><LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE></P>
<P>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</P>
<P>
<TABLE>
<SGMLTBL>
<TBLBODY TBLWD="600">
<TBLCDEFS COLSEP="VDOT" HALIGN="LEFT" CHARPOS="75%" TOPSEP="HDOT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="15" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="70" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="15" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
</TBLCDEFS>
<TBLROWS ROWSEP="HDOT" VALIGN="TOP" LEFTSEP="VDOT">
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" COLSPAN="2" HALIGN="RIGHT">Court File No. CV-19-00619754-0000</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1">&newline;</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" HALIGN="CENTER"><BOLD><EM>ONTARIO</EM></BOLD></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" HALIGN="CENTER"><BOLD>SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE</BOLD></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1">&newline;</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1" COLSPAN="3">BETWEEN:</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1">&newline;</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1" COLSPAN="3" HALIGN="CENTER">2298679 ONTARIO INC. DBA AURUM PROPERTY CARE</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1" COLSPAN="3" HALIGN="CENTER">(FORMERY DBA GOLD STANDARD PROPERTY CARE)</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" COLSPAN="2" HALIGN="RIGHT">Plaintiff</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" HALIGN="CENTER">and</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1" COLSPAN="3" HALIGN="CENTER">NORTHERN HOMECARE SOLUTIONS INC., JOSHUA GOLDKIND,</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1" COLSPAN="3" HALIGN="CENTER">JOSHUA GOLDMAN, JARED HYDE, ANDREW AROUS and RYAN</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" HALIGN="CENTER">EDWARDS</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2" COLSPAN="2" HALIGN="RIGHT">Defendants</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
</TBLROWS>
</TBLBODY>
</SGMLTBL>
</TABLE>
</P></BLOCK1>
<BLOCK1><TI>FACTUM OF THE PLAINTIFF</TI>
<BLOCK2><TI TOCID="I">PART I&mdash;OVERVIEW</TI>
<P>1. The defendants, who include former employees of the plaintiff, covertly accessed the Plaintiff's confidential customer database to steal a customer list for the benefit of a directly competing business. Certain of the defendants have also impersonated the plaintiff in the process.</P>
<P>2. On this motion, the plaintiff seeks an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order and related injunctive relief arising from the defendants' conduct.</P>
<P>3. The plaintiff, Aurum, is a leading Canadian commercial and residential window cleaning and property maintenance company. Aurum is an industry leader servicing government contracts, commercial high-rise buildings, condominium towers, hotels and hospitals, among others.</P>
<P>4. The offending conduct includes:
<P1>(i) 3 former sales employees accessing Aurum's customer list on several occasions after leaving the company. The customer list included the customers' names, addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, and past services, including dates and prices; and</P1>
<P1>(ii) The defendant Joshua Goldman and/or Joshua Goldkind contacting Aurum's customers claiming to be from the company that had serviced them in 20 18, and saying Aurum had changed names to Northern Homecare Solutions. Mr. Goldman has also been claiming that Aurum had &ldquo;problems last year with the operation, so we restructured this year and it is called Northern Home Care now.&rdquo; This, of course, is patently false.</P1></P>
<P>5. The actions of the former employees and the misrepresentations of Mr. Goldman and the team at Northern Homecare have caused Aurum significant loss. This loss continues every day that Northern Homecare is able to continue soliciting Aurum's customer, spreading falsehoods about Aurum's ability to provide services to its customers.</P>
<P>6. Aurum has suffered losses at the hands of the former employees and Northern Homecare in multiple different ways: Aurum has lost customers directly to Northern Homecare by virtue of Northern Homecare soliciting Aurum's customers. Aurum has lost customers because Northern Homecare has been claiming to be the new restructured version of Aurum. Aurum has lost customers because of the appearance of disorganization created by having two different, but seemingly connected companies calling customers to do the same work and appearing to be rescheduling each other's appointments. Aurum has lost customers who were dissatisfied with Northern Homecare's services and attribute the poor service to Aurum. Lastly, with every day that Aurum's customer list is compromised, the possibility of selling the residential division of the business is diminished. No prospective buyer will pay for a compromised customer list.</P>
<P>7. As a result of the actions of its former employees and the actions of the team at Northern Homecare, Aurum has been forced to bring this motion to recover and safeguard the confidential customer information unlawfully taken, and to prevent Northern Homecare from continuing to impersonate Aurum.</P>
<P>8. Specifically, Aurum seeks an injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information; and an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order permitting Aurum to search the Defendants' homes and places of business to seize electronic devices that are likely to have evidence of the Defendants wrongdoings.</P></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI TOCID="II">PART II&mdash;FACTS</TI>
<BLOCK3><TI>The Plaintiff</TI>
<P>9. 2298679 Ontario Inc. is an Ontario company, with its head office in Toronto, Ontario. 2298679 Ontario Inc. carried on business as Gold Standard Property Care until October 30, 2017, after which time it began carrying on business as Aurum Property Care (&ldquo;<BOLD>Aurum</BOLD>&rdquo;).<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Affidavit of Michael Morozov, sworn May 10, 2019 (&ldquo;<BOLD>Morozov affidavit</BOLD>&rdquo;), para. 2, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab D, p. 104. <BOLD>Note:</BOLD> at times, Aurum's sales personnel still refer to the business as Gold Standard Property Care when interacting with residential customers.</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>10. Aurum is a leading Canadian commercial and residential window cleaning and property maintenance company. Aurum is an industry leader servicing government contracts, commercial high-rise buildings, condominium towers, hotels and hospitals, among others.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Morozov affidavit, para. 3, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab D, p. 104-105</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><TI>The Defendants</TI>
<P>11. The Defendant Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. (&ldquo;<BOLD>Northern Homecare</BOLD>&rdquo;) is an Ontario company based out of Thornhill and incorporated April 19, 2018.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Affidavit of Daniel Milgrom, sworn May 13, 2019 (<BOLD>&ldquo;Milgrom Affidavit&rdquo;</BOLD>), para. 38, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 20-21</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> Northern Homecare has advertised and operated its business through the websites www.northerninfo.com, www.northernhomeservices.com and www.northern-homecare.com.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 40, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 21</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>12. The website www.northerninfo.com is registered to Joshua Goldkind at the address 1206 Centre Street, Thornhill, Ontario.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 41, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 21</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>13. Both the websites www.northerninfo.com and www.northernhomeservices.com list the Northern Homecare executive team as Joshua Goldkind, Joshua Goldman, Gabriel Jablonski and Nicholas Hatsios.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 42, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 21</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>14. The Defendant Joshua Goldkind is the founder and Chief Executive Officer of Northern Homecare.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, Ex. 7, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B7, p. 48</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> The Defendant Joshua Goldman is Northern Homecare's Chief Operations Officer.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, Ex. 7, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B7, p. 48</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>15. The Defendant Jared Hyde is a former Aurum employee. He worked for Aurum from May 1, 2017 to August 25, 2018. Hyde was a field business development manager. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 12, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 13</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>16. The Defendant Andrew Arous is a former Aurum employee. He worked for Aurum from April 1, 2018 to July 6, 2018. He was a field business development representative. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 13, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 13</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>17. The Defendant Ryan Edwards is a former Aurum employee. He worked for Aurum from April 1, 2018 to August 2, 2018. He started as a field business development representative, and then was promoted to the role of outbound business development representative on July 23, 2019. In this role he had access to Aurum's residential customer lists, including all customer client information, pricing, and related information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 14, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 14</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><TI>Hyde, Arous and Edwards' terms of employment</TI>
<P>18. The terms of Hyde, Arous and Edwards' employment and their obligations to Aurum were governed by their respective offers of employment and the implied terms of their employment.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, paras. 12-14, Ex. 1-3, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, pp. 13-14, 23-29</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>19. The terms of Hyde, Arous and Edwards' employment, as laid out in their respective employment agreements, included clear and express obligations to protect Au rum's proprietary and confidential information during and after their employment with Aurum.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, paras. 12&ndash;14, Ex. 1-3, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, pp. 13-14, 23&ndash;29</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE>
<QUOTE><BLOCK2><N>7.</N><TI><UNDER>Confidentiality</UNDER></TI>
<P>a. You acknowledge that in the course of your relationship with the Company, you may acquire knowledge and/or information relating to the business, financing and operations of the Company or any of its affiliates all of which is confidential to the Company and its affiliates, as applicable, (collectively, &ldquo;<BOLD>Confidential Information</BOLD>&rdquo;) including, without limitation, customer lists, employee lists, partnership lists, supplier contracts, customer contracts, pricing policies, patents, trademarks and other intellectual property, marketing or product knowledge, technical Information, user manuals and any other information that concerns the Company or any of its affiliates that Is not generally available to the public. You acknowledge that the Company and its affiliates, as applicable, own all fight, title and interest in and to the Confidential Information, and the right to maintain exclusivity of such Confidential information constitutes a proprietary right that the Company is entitled to protect,</P>
<P>b. You acknowledge that Confidential Information could be used to the detriment of the Company., and agree that other than to fulfill the Employee's obligations under the Employment Agreement, you will not (a) use the Confidential Information, directly or Indirectly, for any purpose; (b) disclose to any other person, firm or corporation without the previous consent in writing of the Company, any Confidential Information; or (c) copy or transmit the Confidential information by any means.</P>
<P>c. Upon termination of employment, or at any time at the request of the Company, you will deliver alt copies of Confidential Information in any form whatsoever in your possession, care or control to the Company, and wilt comply with all security measures and to follow all instructions provided by the Company in order to safeguard and protect any Confidential Information.</P>
<P>d. Your obligations with respect to Confidential information do not apply to Information which you can demonstrate: (a) is generally available to or known by the public other than as a result of improper disclosure to you; (b) was rightfully obtained by you from a third party who did not obtain it under an obligation of confidentiality to the Company; or (c) is information which you are obligated to disclose by law, provided that you shall provide prompt notice to the Company of such obligation of disclosure to permit the Company to prevent or limit such disclosure. You will disclose only that portion of the Confidential information which it is advised by written opinion of counsel is legally required.</P>
<P>e. You acknowledge that your obligations with respect to Confidential Information apply both during the term of your employment and survive the termination of your employment, regardless of the reason for termination.</P></BLOCK2></QUOTE></P></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><TI>Northern employees impersonated Aurum</TI>
<P>20. Through reports from various customers, Aurum learned that the Defendants Northern Homecare, Goldkind and/or Goldman obtained Aurum customer information from Hyde, Arous and/or Edwards. They contacted Aurum customers falsely representing to these customers that Aurum had changed its business name to Northern Homecare, and that they were the representatives of Aurum with whom these customers have dealt with in the past.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 21, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>21. In their communications with Aurum's customers, Northern Homecare, Goldkind and/or Goldman referenced or knew of details of past services rendered by Aurum, which were details that only an Aurum employee would have access to, including names, telephone numbers, addresses, nature of previous year's service and date of previous year's service.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 19, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>22. These Defendants utilized the aforesaid confidential information in order to obtain for themselves and for the benefit of their co-Defendants the benefit, goodwill and contractual relationships with its customers that Aurum developed over a number of years at substantial expense.</P>
<P>23. The full details of the Defendants' misrepresentations are not yet known to Aurum. Examples of the Defendants' misrepresentations that are known to Aurum so far include:
<P1>(a) on April 9, 2019, Aurum customer David Shum exchanged emails with Josh at Northern Homecare, who introduced himself as having done Mr. Shum's eaves cleaning the year before. Josh said that Northern Homecare was related to Aurum, and that &ldquo;[t]here were problems last year with the operation, so we restructured the operations this year and it is called Northern Home Care now;&rdquo;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 19&ndash;23, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 15-16</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1>
<P1>(b) Someone called customer Daniel Dico at the end of April 2019 claiming to be from Aurum and wanting to change the time of a scheduled service. When Mr. Dico reviewed his call history, he advised Aurum that that call had come from &ldquo;J Gold-Something&rdquo;;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Affidavit of Joseph Kremer, sworn May 10, 2019 (&ldquo;<BOLD>Kremer Affidavit</BOLD>&rdquo;) paras. 9-10, Tab C</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> and</P1>
<P1>(c) On March 22, 2019, Aurum customer Natalia Duszka advised Aurum that she received a telephone call from a person named Josh who said he was taking over Aurum's clients from last year.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Affidavit of Natalia Dukszta, sworn May 6, 2019, paras. 4&ndash;6, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab E, p. 109</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><TI>Hyde, Arous and Edwards improperly accessed and disseminated Aurum data</TI>
<P>24. After learning that Northern Homecare was impersonating Aurum, Aurum conducted an investigation. Aurum learned that Hyde, Arous and Edwards have each improperly accessed, disclosed, transmitted, disseminated and/or misused Aurum's confidential and proprietary information following the end of their respective employment terms.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 27&ndash;34, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 17&ndash;19</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>25. The full extent of the information accessed, disclosed, transmitted, misappropriated, disseminated and misused, and all of the locations where it is stored are not known to Aurum.</P>
<P>26. The particulars of the breaches available to Aurum at this time are as follows:
<P1>(a) After he was terminated on July 6, 2018, Andrew Arous logged into Aurum's proprietary customer relations management software (called the Window Cleaning Management System, or the &ldquo;<BOLD>WCMS</BOLD>&rdquo;) on at least six occasions: August 29, 2018, December 13, 2018 and February 5, March 15, 19 and 26, 2019;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 33, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 19</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1>
<P1>(b) After he was terminated on August 2, 2018, Ryan Edwards logged into the WCMS on at least two occasions, both on March 5, 2019;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 34, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 19</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1>
<P1>(c) After he was terminated on August 25, 2018 and between September 17, 2018 and March 22, 2019, Jared Hyde accessed and edited six different Aurum Google sheets through his Aurum Gmail account, which contained an Aurum client list and information obtained from the WCMS. These sheets contain customer information and pricing for an Aurum client list. Hyde also access the WCMS on at least 30 occasions.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 27&ndash;31, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 17</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><TI>Connection between the former employees and Northern Homecare</TI>
<P>27. Aurum also established that the persons behind Northern Homecare are in fact connected to the three former employees.</P>
<P>28. Aurum already knew that Hyde and Goldkind had a relationship because it was Hyde who introduced Goldkind to Aurum CEO Michael Morozov for an interview, and because Aurum searched Hyde's Aurum email account and found emails exchanged between Hyde and Goldkind.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 35, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 19-20</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>29. In order to determine whether there is a connection between Arous and Northern Homecare, Hapke (Aurum Vice President of Implementation) conducted some online searches. Northern Homecare has a social media account on the social media platform Instagram. Northern Homecare posts photographs of its work with captions. Other Instagram users are able to &ldquo;like&rdquo; and comment on Northern Homecare's posted photographs. There are numerous examples of posts made by Northern Homecare that have been &ldquo;liked&rdquo; and/or commented on by another Instagram user by the name of &ldquo;andrewarous&rdquo;.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 36, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 20</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>30. The misappropriation of Aurum's data has damaged Aurum's reputation, has resulted in a direct loss of revenue, and has also interfered with the possibility that Aurum might sell its residential customer list, which has been an ongoing possibility of late.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Morozov affidavit, para. 5&ndash;7, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab D, p. 105-106</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>31. The threat to Aurum's interests and the damage suffered by it are ongoing.</P></BLOCK3></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI TOCID="III">PART III&mdash;STATEMENT OF ISSUES, LAW &amp; AUTHORITIES</TI>
<P>32. This Court must decide whether Aurum is entitled to the relief it is seeking, namely:
<P1>(A) an injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information, and prohibiting the Defendants from contacting any persons on Aurum's customer list; and</P1>
<P1>(B) an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order allowing Aurum to enter the Defendants' properties to seize electronic devices for the purpose of collecting evidence of their wrongful conduct.</P1></P>
<BLOCK3><N>A.</N><TI>Aurum is entitled to an injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting its confidential customer information</TI>
<P>33. Aurum is seeking an injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information.</P>
<P>34. A plaintiff seeking an injunction must satisfy three criteria:
<P1>i. that there is a serious issue to be tried;</P1>
<P1>ii. that in the absence of injunctive relief, the moving party will suffer irreparable harm, meaning that the injury could not be adequately compensated by an award of damages; and</P1>
<P1>iii. that the balance of convenience favours granting the injunction, i.e. the harm to the moving party if the injunction is not granted exceeds any harm to the responding party arising from the injunction.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>RJR-MacDonald Inc. v. Canada (Attorney General)</SOC><CITE>[1994] 1 S.C.R. 311</CITE><PAGENUM>at 348</PAGENUM></CASEREF>, Moving Party's Book of Authorities (&ldquo;<BOLD>BOA</BOLD>&rdquo;), Tab 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>35. Each of these three criteria is discussed in turn below.</P>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>i</EM>.</N><TI><EM>Serious issue to be tried</EM></TI>
<P>36. The first part of the test for injunctive relief is whether there is a serious issue to be tried, Also described as a strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case. Aurum has a strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case that the former employee Defendants have committed (a) a breach of contract and a breach of confidence, and (b) that the other Defendants have impersonated Aurum.</P>
<BLOCK5><N><EM>(a)</EM></N><TI><EM>Breach of confidence and breach of contract</EM></TI>
<P>37. The evidence presented on this motion establishes a <EM>prima facie</EM> case that the former employees committed the tort of breach of confidence as well as breach of contract.</P>
<P>38. The tort of breach of confidence is premised on the importance of maintaining confidentiality of information, especially valuable business information. The tort is flexible to allow the courts to craft appropriate remedies that adequately protect important confidential information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Cadbury Schweppes Inc. v. FBI Foods Ltd.</SOC><CITE>[1999] 1 S.C.R. 142</CITE><PARANUM>28</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 5</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> The elements of the test for breach of confidence are as follows:
<P1>(a) The information conveyed must have been confidential;</P1>
<P1>(b) The information must have been communicated in circumstances imparting an obligation of confidence; and</P1>
<P1>(c) There must be unauthorized use (i.e. misuse) of that information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>International Corona Resources Ltd. v. LAC Minerals Ltd.</SOC><CITE>[1989] 2 S.C.R. 574</CITE><PARANUM>10</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 8</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>39. <BOLD><EM>Aurum's customer list is confidential</EM></BOLD>. Aurum's customer list includes: customer name; telephone number; email address; past services provided; price of past services; last execution date (i.e. date of last work); amount collected; and notes, which can include information such as discounts promised for future services (i.e. 20% off next services, etc.). This information is not publicly available. Aurum requires employees to sign a confidentiality agreement before granting access to the list.</P>
<P>40. <BOLD><EM>Aurum imparted the confidential nature of its customer list when it shared the customer list with the former employees</EM></BOLD>. When each of Hyde, Arous and Edwards were hired, they were advised of the confidential nature of Aurum's customer list. They were each asked to sign employment agreements with detailed confidentiality clauses to protect Aurum's customer list.</P>
<P>41. <BOLD><EM>The former employees misused the confidential information</EM></BOLD>. After their employment ended, each of Hyde, Arous and Edwards accessed Aurum's confidential customer information.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 27 <EM>ff</EM>, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 17 <EM>ff</EM></P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> There is good reason to believe that the former employees gave Northern Homecare access to the confidential customer list because Aurum customers have reported that when solicited by Northern Homecare, the Northern Homecare representative had knowledge of past services provided to the customer.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 19, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>42. Since the former employees' contracts laid out breach of confidence as a negative covenant, the above described actions constitute a <EM>prima facie</EM> case for breach of contract as well.</P>
<P>43. In <CASEREF><SOC>Johnson v. Helo Enterprises Inc.</SOC></CASEREF>, this Court held that a strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case of breach of contract was established where an employee secretly copied engineering files and used them after his employment had ended:
<QUOTE><P>I find that this evidence of copying the two engineering files for the MAQ Sonar's design of its sonar device constitutes a <EM>prima facie</EM> case that MAQ Sonar's property was copied and taken by Messrs Ward, Johnson and Spagnuolo. I am also satisfied that such copying of the two engineering files would amount to a prima facie case of a breach of the terms of the employment and confidentiality agreement signed by all of the defendants by counterclaim.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Johnson v. Helo Enterprises Inc.</SOC><CITE>2012 ONSC 5186</CITE><PARANUM>25</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 9</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></QUOTE></P>
<P>44. It is important to note that this is not a case of former employees attempting to use the knowledge and experience they gained in their former employment for the purpose of earning a living with a new employer. Aurum acknowledges that in such a circumstance, this Court might be hesitant to limit the former employees ability to earn a living. This case is different. This appears to be a case of former employees taking their former employers customer list and giving it to a third party. This type of behaviour cannot be tolerated.</P></BLOCK5>
<BLOCK5><N><EM>(b)</EM></N><TI><EM>Impersonation</EM></TI>
<P>45. The evidence presented on this motion also establishes a <EM>prima facie</EM> case that Northern Homecare has impersonated Aurum.
<P1>(a) An Aurum customer reported that a person named Josh contacted them claiming to have provided services to that customer last year;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 15 &amp; 20, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 14-15; Dukszta affidavit, para. 4, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab E, p. 109</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> and</P1>
<P1>(b) An Aurum customer reported that Joshua Goldman told them that Aurum had to change its name due to operation problems the company faced, and so it is now calling itself Northern Homecare Solutions.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Milgrom affidavit, para. 19, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab B, p. 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>46. The above-described evidence shows a sufficiently strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case to justify an injunction prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information and prohibiting the Defendants from contacting any persons on Aurum's customer list.</P></BLOCK5></BLOCK4>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>ii</EM>.</N><TI><EM>The Defendants' conduct will result in irreparable harm if they are not stopped</EM></TI>
<P>47. Irreparable harm has been defined by the courts as either harm which cannot be quantified in monetary terms, or harm of a nature which cannot adequately be compensated for by damages, even if quantifiable in monetary terms.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>RJR-MacDonald v. Canada (Attorney General)</SOC></CASEREF>, <EM>supra</EM> note 26 at 341, BOA, Tab 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>48. The loss of actual or prospective customers, goodwill and diminution of a plaintiff's reputation have been recognized many times over as irreparable harm not compensable in damages. In <CASEREF><SOC>RJR-MacDonald v. Canada</SOC></CASEREF>, the leading case on injunctions, the Supreme Court held that one example of irreparable harm is &ldquo;where one party will suffer permanent market loss or irrevocable damage to its business reputation.&rdquo;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>RJR-MacDonald v. Canada (Attorney General)</SOC></CASEREF>, supra note 26 at 341, BOA, Tab 15</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>49. In <CASEREF><SOC>Canpages Inc. v. Quebecor Media Inc.</SOC></CASEREF>, Justice M. Brown held that &ldquo;loss of actual and potential customers is recognized as irreparable harm not compensable in damages. It is also clear that actual and potential loss of goodwill and diminution of a plaintiff's reputation also constitutes irreparable harm.&rdquo;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Canpages Inc. v. Quebecor Media Inc.</SOC><CITE>2008 CarswellOnt 3193</CITE><PARANUM>12</PARANUM></CASEREF> [<EM>Canpages</EM>], BOA, Tab 6</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> He went on to say:
<QUOTE><P>The loss of goodwill is something that damages cannot reverse. There is evidence that the plaintiff would suffer not only loss of profits and goodwill but also loss of reputation. The loss of actual or potential customers, goodwill and diminution of a plaintiff's reputation have been recognized as irreparable harm not compensable in damages because it is difficult, if not impossible for a plaintiff to establish the extent to which customers were lost by it or gained by the defendant as a result of the impugned conduct. <BOLD><UNDER>In a competitive business market, there is no way for the plaintiff to adequately track the current customers who do not renew contracts, or the prospective customers who do not sign on, due to the interference of the alleged wrongful new competition</UNDER></BOLD>. I am satisfied that the plaintiff will suffer irreparable harm if an interlocutory injunction is not granted.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Canpages</EM>, <EM>supra</EM> note 36 at paras 14, BOA, Tab 6</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> [emphasis added]</P></QUOTE></P>
<P>50. The harm that Aurum has experienced to date includes:
<P1>(a) Aurum has lost customers directly to Northern Homecare by virtue of Northern Homecare having Aurum's customer list and soliciting Aurum's customer.</P1>
<P1>(b) Aurum has lost customers because Northern Homecare has been claiming to be the new restructured version of Aurum.</P1>
<P1>(c) Aurum's reputation has been tarnished due to Northern Homecare and Joshua Goldman claiming that Aurum had problems with its operations last year, requiring it to restructure.</P1>
<P1>(d) Aurum has lost customers because of the appearance of disorganization created by having two different, but seemingly connected companies calling customers to do the same work and appearing to be rescheduling each other's appointments.</P1>
<P1>(e) Aurum has lost customers who were dissatisfied with Northern Homecare's services and attribute the poor service to Aurum.</P1>
<P1>(f) Aurum's ability to sell the residential branch of the business is diminished. No potential buyer will pay money for a customer list that is being used by a competing company</P1>
<P1>(g) Lastly, many of Aurum's commercial customers have developed through residential customers who are also business owners or managers. Aurum has lost out on potential new commercial contracts because of the damage done to its residential business.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Morozov affidavit, para. 5&ndash;7, Moving Party's Motion Record, Tab D, p. 105-106</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>51. Aurum will experience serious harm if the Defendants are not enjoined from continuing to contact Aurum's customers.</P></BLOCK4>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>iii</EM>.</N><TI><EM>The balance of convenience favours granting the injunction</EM></TI>
<P>52. The balance of convenience favours granting the injunction sought by the Plaintiff.</P>
<P>53. Aurum has suffered the misappropriation of a significant volume of customer data at the hands of the Defendants. With every passing day that Aurum is unable to stop the Defendants from soliciting its customers. Aurum is losing business and its reputation is being tarnished. If the Defendants' are not stopped, Aurum will suffer significantly.</P>
<P>54. With respect to the inconvenience that the former employees will experience by the granting of this prohibitive injunction, Hyde, Arous and Edwards willingly agreed to bind themselves to an obligation to return all of Aurum's confidential information at the end of their tenure with the company. They effectively agreed in their employment agreement to what Aurum is seeking by way of prohibitive injunction, and so they cannot very well say that it would be an inconvenience for the Court to grant the order sought.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Toronto Truck Centre Ltd. v. Volvo Trucks Canada Inc.</SOC><CITE>[1998] O.J. No. 2965</CITE><COURTJUR>Gen. Div.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para. 34, BOA, Tab 17</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>55. Specifically with respect to enforcing the terms of the former employees' employment agreements, to the extent that a plaintiff seeks a prohibitive injunction to enforce a negative covenant, it actually does not need prove that it will suffer irreparable harm if the injunction is not granted, nor that the balance of convenience favours granting it an injunction. All that is required is proof of a serious issue to be tried.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Canpages</EM>, <EM>supra</EM> note 36 at para. 8, BOA, Tab 6</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> The former employees, Hyde, Arous and Edwards each signed employment agreements in which they agreed to keep Aurum's customer data confidential. Thus, Aurum is entitled to the requested injunction prohibiting Hyde, Arous and Edwards from keeping copies of and disseminating Aurum's customer data solely based on demonstrating a serious issue to be tried.</P>
<P>56. The situation applies differently to Northern Homecare, Joshua Goldman and Joshua Goldkind because they have no contractual relationship with Aurum. Nonetheless, the balance of convenience weighs in favour of granting this prohibitive injunction against these Defendants as well. These Defendants are being asked to stop contacting Aurum's customers. These Defendants would not have had access to Aurum's customer list but for the wrongful acts of the defendants. Northern Homecare and its executive team cannot claim that they suffer an inconvenience for being forced to give up customer leads that they improperly have in their possession. Further, they cannot claim it is an inconvenience for them to be required to stop impersonating Au rum.</P>
<P>57. A third party who acquires confidential information to which he or she is not entitled may be restrained from using it, even if the third party has no notice of a breach of duty by the person imparting the information to him or her.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Polyresins Ltd. v. Stein-Hall Ltd.</SOC><YEAR>1971</YEAR><CITE>25 D.L.R. (3d) 152</CITE><COURTJUR>Ont. H.C.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para. 23, BOA, Tab 13</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> So, it does not matter whether or not Northern Homecare is aware that the Aurum customer list is confidential. This Court can still order Northern Homecare and its employees to stop using it.</P></BLOCK4></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><N>B.</N><TI>Aurum is entitled to an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order allowing Aurum to enter the Defendants' properties to seize electronic devices</TI>
<P>58. In addition to the relief sought above, Aurum is also entitled to an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order to safeguard the evidence it needs to proceed with its claim against the Defendants.</P>
<P>59. Similar to the test for an injunction, a Plaintiff must establish the following to obtain an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order:
<P1>(a) A strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case on the merits; and</P1>
<P1>(b) The damage to the plaintiff of the defendants' alleged misconduct, potential or actual, is very serious;</P1>
as well as:
<P1>(c) Convincing evidence that the defendant has in its possession incriminating documents or things; and</P1>
<P1>(d) A real possibility that the defendant may destroy such material before the discovery process can do its work.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Celanese Canada Inc. v. Murray Demolition Corp.</SOC><CITE>[2006] 2 S.C.R. 189</CITE><PARANUM>35</PARANUM></CASEREF> [<EM>Celanese</EM>], BOA, Tab 7; <CASEREF><SOC>British Columbia (Attorney General) v. Malik</SOC><CITE>2011 SCC 18</CITE><PARANUM>29</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 3</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>60. In the leading case <CASEREF><SOC>Celanese Canada Inc. v. Murray Demolition Corp.</SOC></CASEREF>, the Supreme Court of Canada recognized that although <EM>Anton Piller</EM> Orders are considered an extraordinary measure, they are useful and necessary tool in the right situation, including a situation in which a defendant's unscrupulous behaviour demonstrates a risk that evidence will be destroyed, altered or moved:
<QUOTE><P>Experience has shown that despite their draconian nature, there is a proper role for Anton Piller orders to ensure that unscrupulous defendants are not able to circumvent the court's processes by, on being forewarned, making relevant evidence disappear. Their usefulness is especially important in the modem era of heavy dependence on computer technology, where documents are easily deleted, moved or destroyed. The utility of this equitable tool in the correct circumstances should not be diminished.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Celanese, ibid</EM>. at para. 32, BOA, Tab 7</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></QUOTE></P>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>i</EM>.</N><TI><EM>Prima facie case</EM></TI>
<P>61. Aurum has established above that it has a strong <EM>prima facie</EM> case against the Defendants. See paragraphs 36 to 46 above.</P></BLOCK4>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>ii</EM>.</N><TI><EM>Serious harm</EM></TI>
<P>62. A Plaintiff may establish serious harm by demonstrating either of the following:
<P1>(a) an inability on the part of a plaintiff to prove its case, either as to liability or damages, should the infringing articles or other vital evidence not be available (the &ldquo;<BOLD>procedural impact approach</BOLD>&rdquo;); or</P1>
<P1>(b) an adverse financial impact (e.g. lost sales and profits, actual or apprehended, as well as harm to the plaintiff's competitive position and reputation) flowing from the defendant's infringement(s) of the plaintiff's rights, which in the plaintiff's circumstances is viewed as being &ldquo;very serious&rdquo; (the &ldquo;<BOLD>adverse financial impact approach</BOLD>&rdquo;)<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Bell ExpressVu Limited Partnership v. Rodgers</SOC><CITE>[2007] O.J. No. 4569</CITE><COURTJUR>S.C.J.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para. 15 [<EM>Bell ExpressVu</EM>], BOA, Tab 2</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>63. Both approaches are satisfied on the facts of this case.</P>
<P>64. <BOLD><EM>Procedural impact approach</EM></BOLD>. Aurum has ample reason to believe that the Defendants are in possession of a significant amount of confidential information belonging to Aurum. Aurum knows that the former employees accessed important confidential information after the end of their employment with Aurum. However, Aurum cannot know the full extent of the confidential information that they possess, with whom they have shared the information and what use they or others have made of it.</P>
<P>65. In order to make out its case and claim the full damages to which it is entitled, Aurum must know the full extent of the information that the Defendants have taken, along with how and when it was used. The extent of the confidential information misappropriated by the Defendants will be an important facet of Aurum's damages claim.</P>
<P>66. In <CASEREF><SOC>Peters &amp; Co. v. Ward</SOC></CASEREF>, the court considered a similar scenario where an employee downloaded a great deal of confidential information in a surreptitious manner prior to the end of his employment. The Alberta Court of Queen's Bench held that serious harm would result to the employer from not being able to retrieve that information and discover what the employee had taken:
<QUOTE><P>It seems to me that in order for the Plaintiff to prove that Mr. Ward had breached his contract, <BOLD>recovery of the downloaded information (which ought not to have been in his possession once he resigned) would be extremely helpful in the ensuing trial</BOLD>.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Peters &amp; Co. v. Ward</SOC><CITE>2014 ABQB 488</CITE><PARANUM>25</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 14</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></QUOTE></P>
<P>67. A similar conclusion is warranted in this case. Auram will experience serious adverse harm under the procedural impact approach if this Anton Piller order is not granted.</P>
<P>68. <BOLD><EM>Adverse Financial Impact Approach</EM></BOLD>. Aurum has dedicated significant time and resources to compiling and maintaining its significant customer database. This database is extremely valuable, especially given the introduction of the National &ldquo;Do Not Call List&rdquo; by the Government of Canada in 2004. The unlawful sharing and use of Aurum's customer list has caused significant damage to Aurum, as described above.</P></BLOCK4>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>iii</EM>.</N><TI><EM>The Defendants have the incriminating evidence in their possession</EM></TI>
<P>69. The Defendants are the ones who are in possession of the lists of customers they have called. Aurum has been able to gather some evidence of the Defendants' wrongdoing by speaking with its customers. However, the bulk of the evidence is in the possession of the Defendants. Absent interviewing every Aurum customer to determine whether they have been contacted by the Defendants, it will not be possible to uncover the extent of the Defendants' wrongdoing without having access to the records in the Defendants' possession.</P></BLOCK4>
<BLOCK4><N><EM>iv</EM>.</N><TI><EM>There is real possibility that the Defendants will destroy the evidence</EM></TI>
<P>70. Courts have acknowledged that it is rare that plaintiff will be able to demonstrate that the defendant has a settled intention to destroy relevant evidence. Instead, the fourth element of the <EM>Celanese</EM> test is met where the plaintiff puts forward evidence regarding the dishonest character of the defendant, and/or the easily disposable nature of the incriminating evidence.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Adobe Systems Inc. v. KLJ Computer Solutions Inc</SOC><CITE>1999 CarswellNat 2490</CITE><PARANUM>37</PARANUM><COURTJUR>F.C.</COURTJUR></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 1</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>71. If Aurum can provide evidence showing the Defendants to be untrustworthy and can establish that materials likely in the Defendants' possession are essential to proving the Aurum's case, there is legitimate fear that the documents might be destroyed and therefore a proper basis for an Anton Piller order.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Nintendo of America Inc. v. Coinex Video Games Inc.</SOC><YEAR>1982</YEAR><CITE>69 C.P.R. (2d) 122</CITE><COURTJUR>C.A.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para 12, BOA, Tab 12 citing <CASEREF><SOC>Yousif v. Salama</SOC><CITE>[1980] 3 All ER 405</CITE><COURTJUR>C.A.</COURTJUR></CASEREF></P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>72. Relevant factors that courts have considered in determining whether the Defendants have demonstrated dishonest character include:
<P1>(a) A history of illegal or otherwise dishonest acts;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Bell ExpressVu</EM>, <EM>supra</EM> note 44 at para. 17, BOA Tab</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1>
<P1>(b) The surreptitious manner in which the incriminating evidence was originally obtained by the defendant;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Brunswick News Inc. v. Langdon</SOC><CITE>2007 NBQB 423</CITE><PARANUM>66-67</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 4</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1>
<P1>(c) The dishonest uses that the defendant has made of the incriminating evidence.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>MD Physician Services Inc. v. Jonathan Financial Inc.</SOC><CITE>20111 ONSC 2409</CITE><PARANUM>25-26</PARANUM></CASEREF>, BOA, Tab 11</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P1></P>
<P>73. In this case, the former employees accessed Aurum's confidential customer information after they were no longer employed by Aurum. This was a dishonest act because the former employees knew they knew they did not have permission to do so.</P>
<P>74. Joshua Goldman's actions are even more reprehensible. He deliberately lied to Aurum customer's about his relationship to Aurum in order to book services with its customers. He claimed to be &ldquo;the one who did their services last year&rdquo; when he has never had any connection to Aurum. He also created the false narrative that Aurum had problems with its operations and had to change its name to Northern Homecare. Certainly there is no explanation for his actions beyond that he was trying to steal Aurum's customers. There is no conceivable explanation for his email exchange with David Shum.</P>
<P>75. Given the unscrupulous behaviour of Aurum's former employees and the Northern Homecare executives, there is a good chance that the Defendants will destroy evidence in their possession if they realize they have been caught.</P>
<P>76. In <CASEREF><SOC>Bell ExpressVu Limited Partnership v. Rogers</SOC></CASEREF>, the court recognized that electronic evidence can easily be destroyed:
<QUOTE><P>Turning to the real risk of destruction or alienation of evidence criterion, Anton Piller orders should not be used as a substitute for the discovery process. That said, again, I agree with Lederman J's conclusion that there was a risk of destruction. He stated that <BOLD>given the nature of the defendants' activity and the fact that much of the evidence was in electronic form that could easily be deleted, there was a real possibility that evidence would be lost if the order was not granted</BOLD>. As stated by Farley J. in <CASEREF><SOC>Ontario Realty Corp v. P. Gabriele &amp; Sons Limited</SOC></CASEREF>:
<QUOTE><P>Traditional judicial methods of discovery are incapable of dealing with many modem cases of patent infringement, trade secret theft, entertainment piracy, etc. <BOLD>Evidence of the infringement, such as computer records</BOLD>, computer programs, and portable electronic circuitry, <BOLD>can easily be erased, destroyed, or hidden,</BOLD> and suppliers of pirate material are both difficult to identify and highly mobile.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Bell ExpressVu</EM>, <EM>supra</EM> note 44 at para. 17, BOA Tab 2 citing <CASEREF><SOC>Ontario Realty Corp v. P. Gabriele &amp; Sons Limited</SOC><CITE>2000 CarswellOnt 4323</CITE><COURTJUR>S.C.J.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para. 13</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P></QUOTE></P></QUOTE></P>
<P>77. The evidence of dishonest and unscrupulous conduct by the Defendants, and the ease with which they could destroy incriminating evidence, provide a compelling basis upon which to draw the inference that the evidence will no longer be available if Au rum is required to follow the regular route of discovery.</P></BLOCK4></BLOCK3>
<BLOCK3><N>C.</N><TI>Aurum is entitled to bring this motion on an <EM>ex parte</EM> basis</TI>
<P>78. This motion is brought without notice to the Defendants. The <EM>Rules of Civil Procedure</EM> allow that, &ldquo;Where the nature of the motion or the circumstances render service of the notice of motion impracticable or unnecessary, the court may make an order without notice.&rdquo;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><EM>Rules of Civil Procedure</EM>, R 37.07(2)</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE></P>
<P>79. Parties must demonstrate some element of &ldquo;extraordinary urgency&rdquo; in order to secure an ex <EM>parte</EM> injunction.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P><CASEREF><SOC>Robert Half Canada Inc. v. Jeewan</SOC><YEAR>2004</YEAR><CITE>71 O.R. (3d) 650</CITE><COURTJUR>S.C.J.</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at paras. 30-31 [<EM>Robert</EM>], BOA, Tab 16</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> &ldquo;Extraordinary urgency&rdquo; arises where &ldquo;the delay necessary to give notice might entail serious and irreparable injury to the plaintiff.&rdquo;<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>Sharpe, R.J., <EM>Injunctions and Specific Performance</EM>, Toronto, Canada Law Book, 1992 at para 2.30, cited in <EM>Robert</EM>, <EM>supra</EM> note 53 at para. 32, BOA, Tab 16</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> Two categories of &ldquo;extraordinary urgency&rdquo; have been observed: (i) where there is good reason to believe that the defendants, if given notice, will act to frustrate the process of justice before the motion can be decided; and, (ii) where there is simply not the time and/or means to provide notice.</P>
<P>80. The first category applies in these circumstances. If the Defendants are given advance notice of this motion, there is a real danger that the purpose of the order sought will be defeated.<FOOTNOTE><FREEFORM><P>See <CASEREF><SOC>Launch! Research &amp; Development Inc. v. Essex Distributing Co.</SOC><CITE>[1977] O.J. No. 1451</CITE><COURTJUR>Sup. Ct. (H.C.J)</COURTJUR></CASEREF> at para. 5, BOA, Tab 10</P></FREEFORM></FOOTNOTE> The Defendants have all behaved in a deceitful manner. There is good reason to believe that, if given notice of a court proceeding, they will act to cover their tracks and frustrate the judicial process.</P></BLOCK3></BLOCK2>
<BLOCK2><TI TOCID="IV">PART IV&mdash;ORDER REQUESTED</TI>
<P>81. Aurum respectfully requests that injunctive relief be granted in accordance with the draft order filed. Aurum further request that an <EM>Anton Piller</EM> order be granted in accordance with the draft order filed.</P>
<P>82. At this time, Aurum is only seeking an <EM>Anton Filler</EM> order to search and seize devices from the Northern Homecare headquarters, as well as Joshua Goldkind's residence.</P>
<P>83. Aurum also requests a sealing order.</P>
<P>84. Finally, Aurum requests its costs on this motion.</P>
<P><BOLD>ALL OF WHICH IS RESPECTFULLY SUBMITTED</BOLD> this 13th day of May, 2019.</P>
<P>&ellip35; Sarah Walker</P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>ROSS BARRISTERS</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON M5V 2E2</LINE></P>
<P><LINE><BOLD>Mark A. Ross LSO# 50872U</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE><BOLD>Sarah Walker LSO# 62427H</BOLD></LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE></P>
<P><LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE></P>
<P>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</P></BLOCK2></BLOCK1>
</FREEFORM>
</FACTUM>
<ORDER LABEL="Order" TYPE="MOTIONORDER"><N>M1.O1</N>
<GRAPHIC FILENAME="2019CARSWELLONT7579M1.O1.PDF"><LINKTEXT>Original Image of this Document (PDF)</LINKTEXT></GRAPHIC>
<DOCTI>Order</DOCTI>
<DATE YYYYMMDD="20190521" LABEL="Date: ">21 MAY, 2019</DATE>
<DECIDER>THE HONOURABLE MR. JUSTICE PERELL</DECIDER>
<CASEREF><SOC>2298679 Ontario Inc. et al. v. Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. et al.</SOC><CITE>2019 CarswellOnt 7579</CITE></CASEREF>
<DOCKET>*****START OF COURT DOCUMENT*****</DOCKET>
<DOCKET LABEL="Court File No. ">19-00619754-0000</DOCKET>
<COURTJUR>ONTARIO SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE</COURTJUR>
<TABLE>
<SGMLTBL>
<TBLBODY TBLWD="600">
<TBLCDEFS COLSEP="VDOT" HALIGN="LEFT" CHARPOS="75%" TOPSEP="HDOT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="47" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="2" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="2" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="2" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
<TBLCDEF COLWD="47" TBLUNITS="PERCENT">
</TBLCDEFS>
<TBLROWS ROWSEP="HDOT" VALIGN="TOP" LEFTSEP="VDOT">
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1">THE HONOURABLE</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3">)</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="4"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="5" HALIGN="RIGHT">TUESDAY, THE 21st</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1">MR. JUSTICE PERELL</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3">)</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="4"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="5"></TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
<TBLROW>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="1"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="2"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="3">)</TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="4"></TBLCELL>
<TBLCELL COLSTART="5" HALIGN="RIGHT">DAY OF MAY, 2019</TBLCELL>
</TBLROW>
</TBLROWS>
</TBLBODY>
</SGMLTBL>
</TABLE>
<PARTYBLOCK>
<LINE>BETWEEN:</LINE>
<PARTY>2298679 ONTARIO INC. DBA AURUM PROPERTY CARE (PREVIOUSLY DBA GOLD STANDARD PROPERTY CARE)</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Plaintiff</PARTYROLE>
<CONNECTOR>and</CONNECTOR>
<PARTY>NORTHERN HOMECARE SOLUTIONS INC., JOSHUA GOLDKIND, JOSHUA GOLDMAN, JARED HYDE, ANDREW AROUS and RYAN EDWARDS</PARTY>
<PARTYROLE>Defendants</PARTYROLE>
</PARTYBLOCK>
<COUNSELBLOCK>
<LAWFIRM>
<FIRMNAME>ROSS BARRISTERS, PROFESSIONAL CORPORATION</FIRMNAME>
</LAWFIRM>
<ADDRESS>
<LINE>123 John Street</LINE>
<LINE>Toronto ON</LINE>
<LINE>M5V 2E2</LINE>
</ADDRESS>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Mark A.</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Ross</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 50872U</LINE>
<LINE>MRoss@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-593-7107</LINE>
<COUNSEL><FIRSNAME>Sarah</FIRSNAME><LASTNAME>Walker</LASTNAME></COUNSEL>
<LINE>LSO# 62427H</LINE>
<LINE>SWalker@rossbarristers.com</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4904</LINE>
<LINE>Tel: 416-572-4910</LINE>
<LINE>Fax: 416-551-8808</LINE>
<LINE>Lawyers for the Plaintiff</LINE>
</COUNSELBLOCK>
<FREEFORM>
<BLOCK1><TI>ORDER FOR INJUNCTIVE RELIEF</TI>
<P><BOLD>THIS MOTION</BOLD>, made without notice to the Defendants for an order prohibiting the Defendants from possessing or transmitting Aurum's confidential customer information in any form or through any medium whatsoever, was heard on Wednesday the 15th day of May 2019 at 393 University Avenue, Toronto, Ontario.</P>
<P><BOLD>ON READING</BOLD> the Notice of Motion, the Affidavits of Daniel Milgrom, Joseph Kremer, Michael Morozov, Natalia Dukszta and Lauren Nixon, the Plaintiff's factum and the Statement of Claim, on hearing the submissions of counsel for the Plaintiff, and on noting the undertaking of the Plaintiff to abide by any Order this Court may make concerning damages arising from the enforcement of this Order,</P>
<P>1. <BOLD>THIS COURT ORDERS</BOLD> that the Defendants and Northern Homecare's officers, directors, servants, agents, employees, and anyone acting on their behalf shall not pass themselves off as carrying on the business of Aurum;</P>
<P>2. <BOLD>THIS COURT ORDERS</BOLD> that the Defendants and the corporate Defendant's officers, directors, servants, agents, employees, and anyone acting on their behalf shall not access, use, or exploit any confidential information of Aurum in their possession including, without limitation, customer lists, employee lists, partnership lists, supplier contracts, customer contracts, pricing policies, patents, trademarks, and other intellectual property;</P>
<P>3. <BOLD>THIS COURT ORDERS</BOLD> that Mr. Goldkind and Northern Homecare shall retain any confidential information of Aurum in their possession including, without limitation, customer lists, employee lists, partnership lists, supplier contracts, customer contracts, pricing, policies, patents, trademarks, and other intellectual property; and</P>
<P>4. <BOLD>THIS COURT ORDERS</BOLD> that Mr. Goldkind and Northern Homecare shall disclose to Aurum within five days of the service of Justice Perell's Reasons for Decision dated May 17, 2019 in an Affidavit of Documents any confidential information of Aurum in their possession including, without limitation, Aurum's customer lists, employee lists, partnership lists, supplier contracts, customer contracts, pricing policies, patents, trademarks, and other intellectual property.</P>
<P>5. <BOLD>THIS COURT ORDERS</BOLD> that this interim injunction and mandatory order shall terminate ten days after the release of Justice Perell's Reasons for Decision dated May 17, 2019, subject to a motion to extend.</P>
<P>&ldquo;Perell. J&rdquo;</P></BLOCK1>
</FREEFORM>
</ORDER>
<MOTIONWRAPPER LABEL="Motion"><N>M1</N>
<SUBTYPE>Factum of the Plaintiff; Order; Motion for Anton Piller Order; Motion for Interim Injunction</SUBTYPE>
<SUBJECT>Corporate and Commercial; Employment; Torts</SUBJECT>
<STATREF><TI>Rules of Civil Procedure</TI>
<REFN>Rule ^RRO1990r194 37.07(2)</REFN></STATREF>
<CASEREF><SOC>2298679 Ontario Inc. et al. v. Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. et al.</SOC><CITE>2019 CarswellOnt 7579</CITE></CASEREF>
<FREEFORM>
<P>M1.F1 Factum of the Plaintiff</P>
<P>M1.O1 Order</P>
</FREEFORM>
</MOTIONWRAPPER>
<PLEADINGWRAPPER LABEL="Pleading">
<N>PWT1</N>
<SUBTYPE>Claim or Originating Document</SUBTYPE>
<DOCTI>Statement of Claim</DOCTI>
<SUBJECT>Corporate and Commercial; Employment; Torts</SUBJECT>
<CASEREF>
<SOC>2298679 Ontario Inc. et al. v. Northern Homecare Solutions Inc. et al.</SOC>
<CITE>2019 CarswellOnt 7579</CITE></CASEREF>
<FREEFORM>
<P>PT1.1 Statement of Claim</P>
</FREEFORM>
</PLEADINGWRAPPER>
</COURTFILE>
</ROOT>